What this means is that the soundness theorem for the Cool type
这意味着Cool类型的可靠性定理
system is a bit more complicated than the one for simple type systems. So in the
系统比用于简单类型系统的系统稍微复杂一些。所以在这里
presence of sub-typing, the, the property that we want is that the static type, computed
在场的子类型化，这个，我们要的属性是静电类型的，计算出来的
by the compiler for a given expression E, is going to be a correct predictor of all
对于给定表达式E的编译器，将是所有表达式的正确预测值
the possible dynamic types that he could have, and we do that by using the sub typing
他可能具有的可能的动态类型，我们通过使用子类型
relationship right here. So we say that with every dynamic type E could have
关系就在这里。所以我们说，对于每一种动态的E类型，
whatever types E can take on at run time, they have to be a sub type of the single static
无论E在运行时可以采用什么类型，它们都必须是单个静电的子类型
type that is predicted for E. What this means is that all the operations that
为E预测的类型。这意味着所有
can be used on an object of type C have to also be able to be used on any object of type
可以在C类型的对象上使用，也必须能够在任何类型的对象上使用
C prime that's a subtype of C. So if C defines certain attributes and methods,
这是C的一个子类型，所以如果C定义了某些属性和方法，
then all of those attributes and methods have to be available in C prime. And therefore
那么所有这些属性和方法都必须在CPrime中可用。因此，
sub classes can only add attributes or methods. So whatever attributes
子类只能添加属性或方法。所以无论什么属性
and methods a sub class will have, what c, c prime in this case, those
以及子类将具有的方法，在本例中为c、c++，即
are all in addition to what c has. So c prime, a sub class, will never remove an attribute
都是在c的基础上增加的。因此，子类c++永远不会删除属性。
or remove a method. It will only extend or add methods and attributes to the
或删除方法。它只会将方法和属性扩展或添加到
class it is inheriting fro M. And note that you're allowed to redefine methods in
类继承自M，请注意，允许您在
cool, and in most object oriented languages, but you cannot change the type.
很酷，在大多数面向对象语言中都是如此，但是您不能更改类型。
So even though you can redefine the code that goes with that method, it still has to
因此，即使您可以重新定义该方法附带的代码，它仍然必须
type check according to the original type that you declared. And so whatever type
根据您声明的原始类型键入check。所以不管是哪种类型
the method has in the first class in which it's defined, it's going to have that
该方法在定义它的第一个类中，它将具有
same type, that same argument and result, the same types for the method arguments,
相同类型、相同的参数和结果、相同的方法参数类型
and the same types for the method result in all of the sub classes. And
并且该方法的相同类型导致所有子类。和
that's a pretty standard, design point for a lot of object oriented languages.
对于许多面向对象的语言来说，这是一个相当标准的设计点。